{
  "u1l1":[
    {
      "question":"The Coptic language evolved from Heiroglyphics.",
      "type":"tf",
      "t":"True",
      "f":"False",
      "ans":"t"
    },
    {
      "question":"What language did many of the Coptic letters come from?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"Greek",
      "b":"Arabic",
      "c":"Russian",
      "d":"Hebrew",
      "ans":"a"
    },
    {
      "question":"Which dialect is primarily used in the Coptic Orthodox Church?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"Fayyumic",
      "b":"Sahidic",
      "c":"Bohairic",
      "d":"Oxyrhincic",
      "ans":"c"
    },
    {
      "question":"What happens when you click on the Coptic (grey) text?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"Nothing",
      "b":"It is said out loud",
      "c":"It turns blue",
      "d":"It turns into english",
      "ans":"b"
    },
    {
      "question":"The words highlighted in blue are vocabulary words.",
      "type":"tf",
      "t":"True",
      "f":"False",
      "ans":"t"
    }
  ],
  "u1l2":[
    {
      "question":"The letter <coptic>a</coptic> sounds like \"ah\".",
      "type":"tf",
      "t":"True",
      "f":"False",
      "ans":"t"
    },
    {
      "question":"What sound does the letter <coptic>q</coptic> make?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"kh",
      "b":"gh",
      "c":"g",
      "d":"k",
      "ans":"a"
    },
    {
      "question":"What sound does the letter <coptic>y</coptic> make?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"a",
      "b":"p",
      "c":"th",
      "d":"sh",
      "ans":"c"
    },
    {
      "question":"What sound does the letter <coptic>[</coptic> make?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"sh",
      "b":"ch",
      "c":"kh",
      "d":"gh",
      "ans":"b"
    },
    {
      "question":"The jinkim adds an extra \"a\" sound before the letter it is above",
      "type":"tf",
      "t":"True",
      "f":"False",
      "ans":"f"
    }
  ],
  "u2l1":[
    {
      "question":"What is a noun?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"An action word",
      "b":"A name",
      "c":"A description word",
      "d":"Not a word!",
      "ans":"b"
    },
    {
      "question":"In Coptic, gender is only for humans.",
      "type":"tf",
      "t":"True",
      "f":"False",
      "ans":"f"
    },
    {
      "question":"What is an adjective?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"An action word",
      "b":"A name",
      "c":"A description word",
      "d":"Not a word!",
      "ans":"c"
    },
    {
      "question":"Why does gender allow sentence structure to have more variety?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"More freedom to rearrange sentence order",
      "b":"More words to choose from",
      "c":"Nouns can be used for everything",
      "d":"I have no idea!",
      "ans":"a"
    },
    {
      "question":"Gender is not very practical for spoken languages.",
      "type":"tf",
      "t":"True",
      "f":"False",
      "ans":"t"
    }
  ],
  "u2l2":[
    {
      "question":"A definite article is used when referring to something in general.",
      "type":"tf",
      "t":"True",
      "f":"False",
      "ans":"f"
    },
    {
      "question":"What does proclitic mean?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"Attaches to the end of a word",
      "b":"Attaches to the beginning of a word",
      "c":"All of the above",
      "d":"Nothing!",
      "ans":"b"
    },
    {
      "question":"What is the singular indefinite article in Coptic?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"<coptic>ou</coptic>",
      "b":"<coptic>han</coptic>",
      "c":"<coptic>pi</coptic>",
      "d":"<coptic>ni</coptic>",
      "ans":"a"
    },
    {
      "question":"What is the plural definite article in Coptic?",
      "type":"mc",
      "a":"<coptic>pi</coptic>",
      "b":"<coptic>ni</coptic>",
      "c":"<coptic>ti</coptic>",
      "d":"<coptic>han</coptic>",
      "ans":"b"
    },
    {
      "question":"To say 'a cat' in Coptic, you would say <coptic>ousau</coptic>.",
      "type":"tf",
      "t":"True",
      "f":"False",
      "ans":"t"
    }
  ]
}